<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Archive 03</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/</link><description>Recent content on Archive 03</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://archive03.online/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is It Time to Invest in Solana ($SOL)? A Look at 2026 Price Predictions</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-11-23-is-it-time/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-11-23-is-it-time/</guid><description>As of November 2025, Solana (SOL) is struggling around the $125 mark. While the launch of the Bitwise ETF is bringing in institutional funds, network stability and token unlock issues are holding it back. What scenarios might unfold in 2026? Three investment assistants engage in a heated debate based on the data.</description></item><item><title>After a Discouraging 2025, Will Altcoins Rebound in 2026?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-11-15-after-a-discouraging/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-11-15-after-a-discouraging/</guid><description>After a year-long Bitcoin rally and altcoin stagnation in 2025, investor fatigue is at an all-time high. Will the long-awaited &amp;lsquo;alt season&amp;rsquo; finally arrive in 2026? We conduct an in-depth analysis of the altcoin market&amp;rsquo;s survival prospects and selective rebound scenarios, based on major token unlock issues, the regulatory environment, and the flow of institutional capital.</description></item><item><title>Why Professor Damodaran Says 'Timing the Market' Is a Losing Game</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-11-11-why-professor-damodaran/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-11-11-why-professor-damodaran/</guid><description>Investment guru Professor Aswath Damodaran warns that while the 2025 U.S. stock market is indeed overvalued, trying to time the market based on this fact is likely to fail. Historical data proves that market timing strategies underperform simple buy-and-hold, and when transaction costs and psychological traps are considered, the losses are even greater.</description></item><item><title>When Will the U.S. Government Shutdown Finally End?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-11-03-when-will-the/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-11-03-when-will-the/</guid><description>The U.S. federal government shutdown has entered its 33rd day, nearing the longest record in history. As tangible damages like the suspension of SNAP food assistance and unpaid federal employee salaries spread, optimistic and pessimistic views on when the shutdown will end are in sharp conflict.</description></item><item><title>Zcash ($ZEC) Hits All-Time High: What Kind of Coin Is It?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-11-02-zcash-zec-hits/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-11-02-zcash-zec-hits/</guid><description>Zcash ($ZEC) is drawing market attention with a 400% surge in just one month. As the leader of privacy coins, optimism surrounding the potential of zero-knowledge proof technology clashes sharply with pessimism warning of strong regulatory risks and a potential bubble collapse.</description></item><item><title>When Will Altcoin Season Finally Arrive? The Growing Anxiety</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-10-31-when-will-altcoin/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-10-31-when-will-altcoin/</guid><description>While Bitcoin smashes all-time highs, why are altcoins so quiet? Pessimism grows that an alt season may not come, clashing with optimism that an explosive rally is imminent, following historical patterns. We&amp;rsquo;ll deeply analyze the current state and future strategies for altcoin investing through data and expert forecasts.</description></item><item><title>Copying the 'God of Investing' Nancy Pelosi? Let's Dive into the $NANC ETF</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-10-27-copying-the-god/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-10-27-copying-the-god/</guid><description>A deep dive into the $NANC ETF, which tracks the stock trades of U.S. Democratic congress members. Is it a chance to replicate Nancy Pelosi&amp;rsquo;s phenomenal returns, or a trap with high fees and time lag issues? Three characters engage in a sharp debate over NANC&amp;rsquo;s investment appeal and potential risks.</description></item><item><title>Bitcoin in Flux: Where Will It Go by Year-End?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-10-26-bitcoin-in-flux/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-10-26-bitcoin-in-flux/</guid><description>With Bitcoin showing mixed signals after hitting a new all-time high, the bullish (Kurumi) and cautious (Mikael) perspectives clash over the year-end price forecast. This post provides an in-depth analysis of two scenarios and investment strategies based on ETF fund flows, on-chain data, and macroeconomic variables.</description></item><item><title>What is UVIX ($UVIX)? And Why It's a Dangerous Investment</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-10-12-what-is-uvix/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-10-12-what-is-uvix/</guid><description>Mew, Kurumi, and Mikael engage in a heated debate about the UVIX ETF, a product that tempts with the allure of ultra-short-term high returns but hides the trap of asset evaporation. They delve into the argument that it can yield massive profits during a market crash versus the critical risk of structural value decay due to contango and leverage decay.</description></item><item><title>The Great Crypto Liquidation of October 11th: What Just Happened?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-10-11-the-great-crypto/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-10-11-the-great-crypto/</guid><description>On October 11, 2025, the crypto market witnessed its largest liquidation event in history, wiping out $19 billion. Sparked by Trump&amp;rsquo;s tariff announcement, Kurumi argues it&amp;rsquo;s a healthy correction and a buying opportunity, while Mikael contends it&amp;rsquo;s the start of a trend reversal, exposing structural vulnerabilities.</description></item><item><title>Ripple (XRP): Time to Buy or Time to Sell?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-10-10-ripple-xrp-time/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-10-10-ripple-xrp-time/</guid><description>After Ripple (XRP)&amp;rsquo;s virtual victory in its long legal battle with the SEC, investors are wondering whether now is a buying opportunity or a time to take profits. Optimists highlight the resolution of legal risks and high growth potential, while skeptics warn that the good news is already priced in and structural risks remain. This post provides an in-depth analysis of the key arguments and risks of investing in XRP to suggest a wise investment strategy.</description></item><item><title>The Bitcoin 4-Year Cycle: Is It Still Valid?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-10-09-the-bitcoin-4-year/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-10-09-the-bitcoin-4-year/</guid><description>The long-held belief in Bitcoin&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;4-year halving cycle&amp;rsquo; is being challenged. With the pre-halving all-time high in 2024 and massive institutional inflows, the market environment is different. Arguments for &amp;rsquo;the cycle is dead&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;it&amp;rsquo;s still valid&amp;rsquo; are fiercely debated. Three AI assistants analyze this hot topic with data.</description></item><item><title>Is the Tech-Heavy $VGT ETF Right for Your Portfolio?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-10-08-is-the-tech-heavy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-10-08-is-the-tech-heavy/</guid><description>We delve into the appeal of VGT, a leading U.S. technology ETF. Between Kurumi&amp;rsquo;s argument for riding the growth of the Fourth Industrial Revolution and Mikael&amp;rsquo;s warnings about concentration and high volatility, we analyze which type of investor is the best fit for VGT.</description></item><item><title>Analyzing the $SPHD ETF: Is It Truly Ideal for Monthly Dividend Income Investors?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-10-02-analyzing-the-sphd/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-10-02-analyzing-the-sphd/</guid><description>We analyze the $SPHD ETF, popular among investors seeking stable cash flow through monthly dividends. While its high dividend yield of over 4% and low volatility are attractive, it has clear limitations like a lack of growth potential and sector concentration. Explore whether SPHD is right for your portfolio through the debate between investors who prioritize stable income over aggressive growth and those who value capital gains.</description></item><item><title>How Reliable Are Support and Resistance Lines on Price Charts?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-28-how-reliable-are/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-28-how-reliable-are/</guid><description>A debate on the reliability of &amp;lsquo;support&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;resistance,&amp;rsquo; the core of technical analysis. Three characters explore the value and inherent risks of these lines, from seeing them as traces of market psychology and a treasure map for timing trades, to the pitfalls of subjective interpretation and lagging indicators.</description></item><item><title>An ETF That Pays Cash Weekly? An In-Depth Look at $MAGY's Pros and Cons</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-27-an-etf-that/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-27-an-etf-that/</guid><description>$MAGY is an ETF that applies a covered call strategy to the &amp;lsquo;Magnificent Seven,&amp;rsquo; providing a high weekly distribution. While it offers the advantage of pursuing both growth and income, it also has clear drawbacks like extreme concentration and limited upside potential. This post provides a deep dive into how $MAGY works and its pros and cons.</description></item><item><title>Energy Powerhouse $CEG: Is It Time to Invest? A Deep Dive into the Pros and Cons</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-24-energy-powerhouse-ceg/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-24-energy-powerhouse-ceg/</guid><description>A deep dive into the investment appeal of Constellation Energy ($CEG), the largest nuclear power company in the U.S. We explore wise investment strategies by comparing the conflicting perspectives of growth expectations driven by the explosive increase in electricity demand in the AI era against the burden of an already high valuation.</description></item><item><title>Analyzing the $SCHX ETF: Who Is It Best For?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-21-analyzing-the-schx/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-21-analyzing-the-schx/</guid><description>We analyze the pros and cons of the $SCHX ETF, one of the cheapest ways to invest in the U.S. large-cap market. Its low 0.03% expense ratio and broad diversification are attractive, but the limitation of having to settle for market average returns is also clear. Discover if $SCHX is right for your portfolio through the debate between a stable investor pursuing the royal road of investing and an aggressive investor aiming for market-beating returns.</description></item><item><title>Fed Cuts Interest Rate by 25bp: What Does It Mean for Bitcoin?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-18-fed-cuts-interest/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-18-fed-cuts-interest/</guid><description>The U.S. Federal Reserve has cut its benchmark interest rate by 25bp, signaling a turning point in the era of high interest rates. This brings both the hope of increased liquidity for the Bitcoin market and the fear of a recession signal. This post analyzes the potential positive and negative impacts of the rate cut on Bitcoin from multiple angles.</description></item><item><title>Building a Pension with Dividends? Let's Dive into the $SCHD ETF</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-16-building-a-pension/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-16-building-a-pension/</guid><description>A deep dive into America&amp;rsquo;s leading dividend growth ETF, $SCHD. Through a debate between Kurumi, who champions its steady cash flow and stability, and Mikael, who points out its growth limitations and interest rate risks, find out if $SCHD is the right fit for your retirement portfolio.</description></item><item><title>Fallen Giant Intel: A Comeback Story? Analyzing Opportunities and Pitfalls</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-15-fallen-giant-intel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-15-fallen-giant-intel/</guid><description>Intel, the once-dominant semiconductor empire, is attempting a revival with its &amp;lsquo;IDM 2.0&amp;rsquo; strategy. We conduct an in-depth analysis of Intel&amp;rsquo;s future, weighing the potential success of its foundry business and entry into the AI chip market against the technological uncertainty of its 18A process and a fiercely competitive landscape.</description></item><item><title>Why is Binance Coin ($BNB) Set to Benefit from the Alt-Season?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-15-why-is-binance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-15-why-is-binance/</guid><description>As excitement builds for an &amp;lsquo;alt-season&amp;rsquo; in the second half of 2025, we take a deep dive into the investment value of Binance Coin ($BNB), the native currency of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest exchange. While the BNB Chain&amp;rsquo;s technical advancements and strong token burn model boost its growth potential, it also faces clear limitations, such as its dependency on the Binance exchange and centralization risks. Three distinct characters debate whether BNB can become the biggest beneficiary of the alt-season and what potential dangers lie in wait.</description></item><item><title>[Special Edition] Review of the Sci-Fi Novel 'The Moon Is a Harsh Mistress'</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-07-special-edition-review/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-07-special-edition-review/</guid><description>An in-depth analysis of the classic sci-fi novel &amp;lsquo;The Moon Is a Harsh Mistress.&amp;rsquo; Through a debate between Kurumi, who is passionate about the revolutionary narrative of lunar independence, and Mikael, who sharply criticizes the violence of the process and the dangers of political idealism, we explore the work&amp;rsquo;s significance and dilemmas.</description></item><item><title>How Far is Tesla's Optimus From Commercialization?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-07-how-far-is/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-07-how-far-is/</guid><description>Three characters debate the commercialization timeline for Tesla&amp;rsquo;s humanoid robot, &amp;lsquo;Optimus.&amp;rsquo; They analyze Elon Musk&amp;rsquo;s ambitious vision against technological realities and production delays, diagnosing Optimus&amp;rsquo;s potential impact on humanity&amp;rsquo;s future and the risks it currently faces.</description></item><item><title>NVIDIA ($NVDA): Is the Next Big Thing Humanoid Robots?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-01-nvidia-nvda-is/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-01-nvidia-nvda-is/</guid><description>NVIDIA, the king of AI chips, is making a serious move into the humanoid robot market. Three experts engage in an in-depth discussion about NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s grand plan to generate revenue from both robot training and execution, and the potential risks, including the technological and safety hurdles that must be overcome before this translates into actual sales.</description></item><item><title>Chainlink ($LINK): A Deep Dive into the Oracle King, Price Analysis, and Future Outlook</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-30-chainlink-link-a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-30-chainlink-link-a/</guid><description>As the core infrastructure connecting blockchains to the real world, does Chainlink ($LINK) have a bright future? We dive into a sharp debate between Kurumi, who champions Chainlink&amp;rsquo;s monopolistic position and growth potential as a Web3 necessity, and Mikael, who warns of potential risks like market dependency and uncertain tokenomics, to analyze the pros and cons of investing in $LINK.</description></item><item><title>Market Expects September Rate Cut: Will the 'Money Move' Begin?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-30-market-expects-september/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-30-market-expects-september/</guid><description>The U.S. Federal Reserve&amp;rsquo;s September rate cut expectations are at an all-time high. Is this a signal for the start of a new bull market, or a precursor to a recession? We analyze the direction of the &amp;lsquo;money move&amp;rsquo; through a sharp debate between Kurumi, who anticipates a liquidity rally, and Mikael, who warns of hidden risks.</description></item><item><title>Powell's Dovish Turn: The Fallout from the 2025 Jackson Hole Meeting</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-23-powells-dovish-turn/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-23-powells-dovish-turn/</guid><description>At the 2025 Jackson Hole meeting, Fed Chair Jerome Powell pivoted to a dovish stance, sparking market euphoria. As expectations for a rate cut grow, three distinct characters engage in a fierce debate, weighing the optimism against the underlying risks of an economic slowdown and inflation.</description></item><item><title>A Warning from Howard Marks, the 'Sage of Wall Street': Is It Time to Sell?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-17-a-warning-from/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-17-a-warning-from/</guid><description>This post analyzes the current market&amp;rsquo;s overvaluation risk through Oaktree Capital&amp;rsquo;s Howard Marks&amp;rsquo; latest memo, &amp;lsquo;The Calculus of Value.&amp;rsquo; It explores the clash between Mikael&amp;rsquo;s warning of a &amp;lsquo;worrisome&amp;rsquo; situation where prices rise despite worsening fundamentals, and Kurumi&amp;rsquo;s optimism that the new era led by the AI revolution justifies high valuations, seeking a wise investment strategy.</description></item><item><title>How High Can Dogecoin ($DOGE) Go This Year?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-14-how-high-can/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-14-how-high-can/</guid><description>As expectations for an altcoin season grow with the decline in Bitcoin dominance, we explore the future of the original memecoin, Dogecoin ($DOGE). We analyze its growth potential from the massive catalyst of X (formerly Twitter) payment system integration against its inherent risk of lacking fundamentals, forecasting its price targets for the second half of the year.</description></item><item><title>Ethereum Breaks $4,000: Is This the Starting Gun for Altseason?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-09-ethereum-breaks-4000/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-09-ethereum-breaks-4000/</guid><description>With Ethereum surpassing the $4,000 mark, anticipation for a full-blown altseason is growing. Three distinct characters engage in a deep discussion centered on data, growth potential, and potential risks to determine whether this is the signal for a new opportunity or a warning sign of an overheated market.</description></item><item><title>Pharma ETF $PPH: A Deep Dive into Its Allure and Pitfalls</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-09-pharma-etf-pph/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-09-pharma-etf-pph/</guid><description>A deep-dive analysis of the VanEck Pharmaceutical ETF ($PPH). Three characters debate the explosive growth potential of its concentrated strategy, focusing on innovators like Eli Lilly, against the clear pitfalls of high valuation and concentration risk.</description></item><item><title>Ondo Finance ($ONDO): A Deep Dive into the RWA Leader</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-08-ondo-finance-ondo/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-08-ondo-finance-ondo/</guid><description>A deep dive into Ondo Finance ($ONDO), the emerging leader in Real-World Asset (RWA) tokenization. Between its growth potential through a partnership with BlackRock and the potential risks of regulation and centralization, three characters fiercely debate the pros and cons of this new financial innovation.</description></item><item><title>Retirement Funds Meet Crypto: The $43 Trillion Impact?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-08-retirement-funds-meet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-08-retirement-funds-meet/</guid><description>A fierce debate erupts over the Trump administration&amp;rsquo;s executive order to allow cryptocurrency in retirement funds. One side argues it&amp;rsquo;s a massive opportunity to unlock a $43 trillion market, while the other contends it&amp;rsquo;s a dangerous gamble that could destroy investors&amp;rsquo; futures.</description></item><item><title>Meta Is Eating the Internet — Should You Invest Now?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-07-whats-the-investment/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-07-whats-the-investment/</guid><description>We analyze the investment prospects for Meta ($META), the empire of Facebook and Instagram. Amid the explosive growth of its AI-powered advertising business and the astronomical investment risks of Reality Labs, three characters engage in a fierce debate over Meta&amp;rsquo;s future value.</description></item><item><title>$EEM vs. $EMXC: Which Emerging Markets ETF is the Better Bet?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-05-eem-vs-emxc/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-05-eem-vs-emxc/</guid><description>The core dilemma of emerging markets investing: to include China or not? This post provides an in-depth comparison of $EEM, a classic ETF that includes China, and $EMXC, which excludes it. Three characters debate the pros and cons of the traditional approach of embracing China&amp;rsquo;s risk versus the new strategy of avoiding &amp;lsquo;China risk&amp;rsquo; and betting on the growth of India, Taiwan, and others.</description></item><item><title>'Cash is King!' Why is Warren Buffett Continuously Selling Stocks?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-03-cash-is-king/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-03-cash-is-king/</guid><description>Berkshire Hathaway, led by the sage of investing Warren Buffett, is amassing a record level of cash and selling Apple stock. Dive into a sharp debate among three girls about whether this is a danger sign heralding a market crash or preparation for a massive opportunity.</description></item><item><title>IonQ ($IONQ), a Leader in Quantum Computing: What's the Investment Outlook?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-03-ionq-ionq-a/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-03-ionq-ionq-a/</guid><description>IonQ ($IONQ) is a frontrunner in quantum computing technology, carrying high expectations of becoming the &amp;rsquo;next NVIDIA.&amp;rsquo; However, it also faces clear risks, such as a high valuation and financial instability. This post provides an in-depth analysis of IonQ&amp;rsquo;s growth potential and investment risks, offering a balanced perspective on this innovative company.</description></item><item><title>Betting on Aerospace? An Analysis and Price Outlook for $ARKX</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-02-betting-on-aerospace/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-02-betting-on-aerospace/</guid><description>An in-depth analysis of $ARKX, the space exploration ETF managed by Cathie Wood&amp;rsquo;s ARK Invest. Three girls discuss the growth potential of its portfolio, which invests in various sectors beyond pure space technology—such as defense, communications, and UAM—as well as the criticisms of it being a &amp;lsquo;quasi-space ETF&amp;rsquo; and its high volatility risks.</description></item><item><title>Is Now the Time to Buy Kaia ($Kaia) Coin? An Analysis and Investment Outlook</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-02-is-now-the/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-02-is-now-the/</guid><description>Three distinct personas debate the investment value of Kaia ($Kaia) coin, born from the merger of Kakao&amp;rsquo;s Klaytn and Line&amp;rsquo;s Finschia. They sharply analyze its overwhelming potential as Asia&amp;rsquo;s largest Web3 ecosystem against the potential risks of integrating two giant projects and their past limitations, arguing whether now is the right time to invest.</description></item><item><title>Solana, the 'Ethereum Killer': What's the Investment Outlook for 2025?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-02-solana-the-ethereum/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-02-solana-the-ethereum/</guid><description>A deep dive into the 2025 investment value of Solana ($SOL), the &amp;lsquo;Ethereum Killer&amp;rsquo; of the crypto market. Three distinct characters engage in a sharp debate over its growth potential, driven by overwhelming speed and explosive ecosystem growth, versus its fundamental risks concerning network stability and decentralization.</description></item><item><title>AI ETF Showdown: BOTZ vs. AIQ, Which Is Your Pick?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-29-ai-etf-showdown/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-29-ai-etf-showdown/</guid><description>A deep-dive comparison of the two most representative ETFs for investing in the AI revolution: BOTZ and AIQ. We&amp;rsquo;ll explore the pros and cons of BOTZ, which focuses on robotics hardware, and AIQ, which diversifies across the entire AI ecosystem, to see which ETF is better suited for different types of investors.</description></item><item><title>Samsung to Build Tesla's Next-Gen Chip? What It Means for Investors</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-29-samsung-to-build/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-29-samsung-to-build/</guid><description>The news that Samsung Electronics will produce Tesla&amp;rsquo;s next-generation self-driving chip is drawing attention as a massive deal that could change the foundry market landscape. While it&amp;rsquo;s an opportunity to secure core technology for future industries, it&amp;rsquo;s also a double-edged sword, involving fierce competition with TSMC and risks in the actual mass production process.</description></item><item><title>What Does the Dollar Index (DXY) Have to Do with My Investments?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-27-what-does-the/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-27-what-does-the/</guid><description>Discover how the Dollar Index (DXY) impacts your investments in stocks, crypto, and more. Explore whether a strong or weak dollar presents an opportunity or a crisis through the conflicting perspectives of Kurumi and Mikael, and learn to navigate the flow of global money to build your investment strategy.</description></item><item><title>'Altcoin King' Ethereum: Price Outlook for H2 2025?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-21-altcoin-king-ethereum/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-21-altcoin-king-ethereum/</guid><description>We analyze the price outlook for Ethereum in the second half of 2025, which is drawing intense interest with the launch of a U.S. spot ETF. Three characters engage in a sharp debate, weighing the massive tailwind of institutional capital inflow against potential risks like intensifying competition from Solana and macroeconomic uncertainty.</description></item><item><title>Coca-Cola ($KO): Is Warren Buffett's 'Golden Goose' Still Viable in 2025?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-18-coca-cola-ko-is/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-18-coca-cola-ko-is/</guid><description>From a 2025 perspective, we re-evaluate the investment value of Coca-Cola ($KO), a stock beloved by investing legend Warren Buffett. Through a sharp debate between Kurumi, who champions its stability and brand power backed by 63 years of dividend increases, and Mikael, who points out the risks of stagnant growth and health trends, we analyze the pros and cons of this &amp;lsquo;Dividend King&amp;rsquo;.</description></item><item><title>The GENIUS Act: A Stroke of Genius That Could Change the Crypto Market?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-18-the-genius-act/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-18-the-genius-act/</guid><description>Three girls engage in a heated debate over the &amp;lsquo;GENIUS Act&amp;rsquo; passed by the U.S. Congress. Through Kurumi&amp;rsquo;s arguments for explosive growth from crypto&amp;rsquo;s institutional adoption and Mikael&amp;rsquo;s sharp analysis of the risks of contagion to the traditional financial system, they delve into the pros and cons of stablecoin regulation.</description></item><item><title>The 'DeFi Bank' $AAVE: What Kind of Coin Is It? Price Forecast and Analysis</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-15-the-defi-bank/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-15-the-defi-bank/</guid><description>A deep-dive analysis into the potential and risks of Aave ($AAVE), a leading DeFi lending protocol. Three characters engage in a sharp debate on its growth potential through its native stablecoin $GHO, and key issues like smart contract risks, liquidation, and regulatory challenges.</description></item><item><title>Palantir ($PLTR), the Darling of the AI Age: Is It Still a Good Time to Invest?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-13-palantir-pltr-the/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-13-palantir-pltr-the/</guid><description>A fierce debate unfolds over the future of Palantir ($PLTR), the rising star of the AI era. We analyze the pros and cons of investing in $PLTR through the arguments of Kurumi, who champions its explosive commercial growth, and Mikael, who warns of its killer valuation and shareholder dilution.</description></item><item><title>Betting on Disruption: A Deep Dive into Cathie Wood's Investment Philosophy</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-12-betting-on-disruption/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-12-betting-on-disruption/</guid><description>This post explores the debate surrounding Cathie Wood&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;disruptive innovation&amp;rsquo; investment philosophy. It contrasts the growth strategy of betting boldly on future technologies for explosive returns with the risk management perspective that warns against the dangers of speculation that ignores valuation.</description></item><item><title>Bitcoin Breaks All-Time High: What Does It Truly Mean?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-10-bitcoin-breaks-all-time/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-10-bitcoin-breaks-all-time/</guid><description>Bitcoin has shattered its all-time high, surpassing $112,000. Three distinct personas sharply debate the growth potential driven by institutional inflows and regulatory optimism against the potential risks fueled by excessive greed and historical patterns.</description></item><item><title>How Could Robinhood Offer Commission-Free Trading?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-09-how-could-robinhood/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-09-how-could-robinhood/</guid><description>Unpacking the secret behind Robinhood&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;zero commission&amp;rsquo; model. Three characters debate the pros and cons of Payment for Order Flow (PFOF), weighing the innovation of &amp;lsquo;democratizing finance&amp;rsquo; against the risks of &amp;lsquo;hidden costs&amp;rsquo; and conflicts of interest.</description></item><item><title>The Dividend Aristocrat Portfolio: Can I Build One Too?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-08-the-dividend-aristocrat/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-08-the-dividend-aristocrat/</guid><description>Explore the allure and risks of a &amp;lsquo;Dividend Aristocrat&amp;rsquo; portfolio. Three distinct characters debate the pros (steady cash flow, compounding) and cons (limited growth, interest rate risk) of investing in stable companies that have increased dividends for over 25 years.</description></item><item><title>Ray Dalio's Warning: How Should Individual Investors Respond?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-05-ray-dalios-warning/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-05-ray-dalios-warning/</guid><description>In response to world-renowned investor Ray Dalio&amp;rsquo;s warning of a great collapse in order, growth-focused investment strategies (Kurumi) clash with risk-management-focused strategies (Mikael). This post explores new investment opportunities like cash-rich companies, consumer staples, and AI technology, while also discussing the importance of currency diversification, gold investment, and geopolitical risk management to find a balanced response for individual investors.</description></item><item><title>JEPI vs. JEPQ: Stability or Growth? Unpacking the Ultimate Monthly Dividend ETFs</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-04-jepi-vs-jepq/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-04-jepi-vs-jepq/</guid><description>A comparative analysis of America&amp;rsquo;s leading monthly dividend covered call ETFs, JEPI and JEPQ. We break down the pros and cons of the stable, S&amp;amp;P 500-based JEPI and the high-yield, Nasdaq 100-based JEPQ, helping you find the perfect fit for your investment style.</description></item><item><title>The Classic 60/40 Portfolio: Still Relevant in 2025?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-04-the-classic-6040/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-04-the-classic-6040/</guid><description>Three girls debate the validity of the classic &amp;lsquo;60/40 portfolio.&amp;rsquo; Kurumi champions its proven simplicity and stability, while Mikael warns of the potential for simultaneous stock and bond declines, arguing that times have changed. We analyze whether this traditional asset allocation strategy can still succeed today.</description></item><item><title>How Did John Bogle's 'Buy Everything' Philosophy Change the History of Investing?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-03-john-bogle/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-03-john-bogle/</guid><description>We delve into the investment philosophy of John Bogle, the &amp;lsquo;Saint of Wall Street.&amp;rsquo; Kurumi explains how the revolutionary idea of &amp;rsquo;low-cost index funds&amp;rsquo; provided individual investors with a new path to wealth accumulation, while Mikael points out the limitations and structural risks of a strategy that can only ever achieve the &amp;lsquo;average.&amp;rsquo; How should we apply the wisdom of this so-called cornerstone of investing?</description></item><item><title>Is the Fed's Rate Cut Really Good News for the Stock Market?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-03-is-the-feds/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-03-is-the-feds/</guid><description>Three characters clash over the impact of the U.S. Federal Reserve&amp;rsquo;s interest rate cut on the market. Kurumi predicts a bull market, cheering for a liquidity party, while Mikael strongly warns it&amp;rsquo;s a precursor to a recession. We analyze the two faces of rate cuts through historical data and explore the wise stance investors should take.</description></item><item><title>Tesla ($TSLA): A Good Time to Invest? Analyzing Opportunities &amp; Risks</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-03-tesla-tsla-a/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-03-tesla-tsla-a/</guid><description>Tesla&amp;rsquo;s future: An AI robotics company or a car manufacturer in crisis? Kurumi presents a grand vision of Robotaxis and Optimus, while Mikael points to declining sales and CEO risk. We conduct an in-depth diagnosis of the opportunities and weaknesses of investing in Tesla.</description></item><item><title>VTI vs. VOO: Which Vanguard ETF Is Right for You?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-03-vti-vs-voo/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-03-vti-vs-voo/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s the timeless debate for US stock investors: VTI vs. VOO. Kurumi argues for VTI&amp;rsquo;s ability to capture future growth by buying the &amp;rsquo;total market,&amp;rsquo; while Mikael contends that VOO&amp;rsquo;s focus on 500 proven winners is more efficient. We break down the subtle philosophical differences and nearly identical performance data to help you choose.</description></item><item><title>Decoding a Wall Street Giant: The Richard Bernstein Method</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-02-richard-bernstein/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-02-richard-bernstein/</guid><description>Three unique characters dissect the investment philosophy of Wall Street giant Richard Bernstein. A fierce debate ensues over his top-down &amp;lsquo;see the forest&amp;rsquo; approach and the contrarian core of enduring pain. Learn his wisdom of finding market opportunities through corporate profit cycles.</description></item><item><title>The 10-Year Rule: Why Long-Term Investing Is Your Greatest Ally</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-01-10-years/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-01-10-years/</guid><description>Why is a 10-year investment horizon so critical? From harnessing the &amp;lsquo;magic of compounding&amp;rsquo; that Einstein praised, to using S&amp;amp;P 500 data to prove how time slashes market risk, and escaping the psychological traps of fear and greed. Three unique characters break down the three essential reasons for long-term investing.</description></item><item><title>Glenn Gould's Forte: The Pianist's Secret to Winning at the Market</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-30-glenn-gould/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-30-glenn-gould/</guid><description>Discover the surprising investing prowess of legendary pianist Glenn Gould. How did he tune out market noise to become a successful long-term investor? Three unique characters analyze his investment philosophy and portfolio, exploring the two sides of his genius: disciplined, emotion-free principles and a profound belief in what he loved.</description></item><item><title>Is Crypto About to Explode? Decoding the Bullish News for July</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-30-crypto-news/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-30-crypto-news/</guid><description>With July just around the corner, the crypto market is buzzing. Rumors of a US government BTC roadmap, infrastructure build-outs, and Trump&amp;rsquo;s expected signature on a stablecoin bill have sparked unprecedented hype. Kurumi cheers for the dawn of a new era, while Mikael delivers a cold warning about the dangers of unrealized expectations. See the clash of opinions.</description></item><item><title>S&amp;P 500 Hits All-Time High: What Does It Mean?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-29-sp500/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-29-sp500/</guid><description>The S&amp;amp;P 500 has soared past 6,100 to a new record. Kurumi cheers for the dual engines of AI-driven earnings and easing geopolitical risks, while Mikael warns of Dot-com bubble valuations and &amp;lsquo;Extreme Greed.&amp;rsquo; Is it time to hit the accelerator, or should you be looking for the emergency exit?</description></item><item><title>Sunspots and Bull Markets: A Cosmic Connection?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-27-financial-astrology/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-27-financial-astrology/</guid><description>Is there really a link between sunspots and stock market bull runs? Three girls clash over this mystical theory, which dates back to a 19th-century economist. Through Mikael&amp;rsquo;s sharp analysis refuting the science and Kurumi&amp;rsquo;s insistence on the &amp;lsquo;power of story,&amp;rsquo; we explore what this old legend truly means for modern investors.</description></item><item><title>XRP Down 40%: Time to Buy the Dip or Abandon Ship?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-27-xrp-review/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-27-xrp-review/</guid><description>Your friend bought Ripple (XRP) at the top and is now facing a huge loss. Is averaging down now an opportunity or a trap? Kurumi&amp;rsquo;s hope, fueled by the expected end of the SEC lawsuit, clashes with Mikael&amp;rsquo;s stark warning about extreme volatility and remaining risks. The three heroines provide an urgent diagnosis to save your friend&amp;rsquo;s portfolio.</description></item><item><title>Nvidia Hits All-Time Highs: Bubble or Just the Beginning?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-26-nvidia-review/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-26-nvidia-review/</guid><description>Nvidia has shattered its all-time high. Is this a celebration of the AI era, or a dangerous bubble? Kurumi&amp;rsquo;s optimism, fueled by the AI market&amp;rsquo;s structural growth and the powerful CUDA ecosystem, clashes head-on with Mikael&amp;rsquo;s warnings of extreme valuations and intensifying competition. Three unique characters engage in a fierce debate over Nvidia&amp;rsquo;s future.</description></item><item><title>Taming the FOMO: How to Conquer the Investor's Worst Enemy</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-26-fomo/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-26-fomo/</guid><description>The fear of missing out, or FOMO. Kurumi argues it&amp;rsquo;s a chance to capture market energy, while Mikael warns it&amp;rsquo;s a destructive game of passing the bomb. Three unique characters break down the true nature of this psychological trap and reveal how to overcome it.</description></item><item><title>Robinhood: Why Cathie Wood is Betting Big on $HOOD</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-25-robinhood/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-25-robinhood/</guid><description>Cathie Wood keeps buying Robinhood ($HOOD). It&amp;rsquo;s a battleground between the innovation of &amp;lsquo;democratizing finance&amp;rsquo; and the critical risks of PFOF regulations and an SEC lawsuit. Kurumi sees a next-gen super-app, while Mikael warns of the regulatory sword. See the data and decide for yourself.</description></item><item><title>The Dawn of the Digital Won: What a KRW Stablecoin Means for Investors</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-25-won-stable-coin/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-25-won-stable-coin/</guid><description>The launch of a Korean Won stablecoin: Will it be the next STO craze or a new investment frontier? Kurumi bets on the explosive growth of issuer stocks and mainnet tokens, while Mikael warns of priced-in hype and the limits of a domestic-only market. We analyze the opportunities and pitfalls of owning a piece of future financial infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Why the Stock Market Isn't a Zero-Sum Game</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-25-non-zero-sum-game/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-25-non-zero-sum-game/</guid><description>Did you think stock investing was a game of taking someone else&amp;rsquo;s money? From the theory that it&amp;rsquo;s a &amp;lsquo;positive-sum game&amp;rsquo; where the whole pie grows thanks to corporate value creation, to the reality that short-term trading has the brutal nature of a &amp;lsquo;zero-sum game&amp;rsquo;—our three experts clearly define the true nature of investing.</description></item><item><title>Google ($GOOGL) is 'Historically Cheap'—Is It Time to Buy?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-24-google-review/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-24-google-review/</guid><description>Google ($GOOGL) has entered a historically undervalued range. Kurumi&amp;rsquo;s optimism about its explosive growth potential in AI and Cloud clashes head-on with Mikael&amp;rsquo;s pessimism, who warns of massive antitrust legal risks. Is investing in Google now a wise choice?</description></item><item><title>Is It Time to Buy the Dip on Samsung Electronics?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-24-samsung-review/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-24-samsung-review/</guid><description>Samsung Electronics faces both hopes for a semiconductor industry turnaround and the challenge of securing its HBM competitiveness. Is its ₩60,000 stock price undervalued, or a reasonable reflection of its risks? Three unique characters engage in a fierce debate about Samsung&amp;rsquo;s present and future.</description></item><item><title>JEPI's 7% Yield: A Retirement Dream or a Total Return Trap?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-22-jepi-etf-analysis/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-22-jepi-etf-analysis/</guid><description>JEPI ETF offers a high distribution yield of over 7%, like monthly rent. Three unique characters fiercely debate the allure of its covered call strategy against its fatal flaws, including underperformance in bull markets and the risk of principal erosion. Is JEPI truly the best choice for those preparing for retirement?</description></item><item><title>Bitcoin: Is It Really a Valuable Asset?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-21-bitcoin-value/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-21-bitcoin-value/</guid><description>Is Bitcoin an innovative asset or a speculative bubble? Kurumi&amp;rsquo;s optimism about &amp;lsquo;Digital Gold&amp;rsquo; clashes with Mikael&amp;rsquo;s skepticism, who warns of its lack of intrinsic value and regulatory risks. Based on data about market cap, supply, and institutional adoption, our three heroines debate the true value of Bitcoin.</description></item><item><title>How to Start Investing in Bonds: Your Ally in a Bear Market?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-21-bond-investment-guide/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-21-bond-investment-guide/</guid><description>Are bonds truly a safe haven when the stock market is volatile? From their negative correlation with stocks and predictable cash flow to the risks of interest rates and opportunity costs. Three unique characters break down everything you need to know about bond investing, including key ETFs like TLT, IEF, and AGG.</description></item><item><title>Should You Invest in Gold During Inflation? Here’s How to Start</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-21-gold-investment-guide/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-21-gold-investment-guide/</guid><description>Amidst persistent inflation and geopolitical risks, is &amp;lsquo;gold&amp;rsquo; truly a safe haven? From attractive opportunities to fatal risks, and covering everything from the KRX Gold Market to Gold ETFs, three non-human girls will give you a clear and refreshing analysis.</description></item><item><title>Why Did Trump Call Powell 'Stupid'?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-20-trump-criticizes-powell/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-20-trump-criticizes-powell/</guid><description>President Trump has publicly criticized Fed Chair Powell, pressuring him to cut interest rates. Mew, Kurumi, and Mikael sharply analyze the current situation, where the hope for a short-term market boost clashes with the immense risk of undermining the central bank&amp;rsquo;s independence.</description></item><item><title>Auto-Farming Your Investments? The Meaning, Advantages, and Limits of Passive Investing</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-18-passive-investing-guide/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-18-passive-investing-guide/</guid><description>In the world of investing, can &amp;lsquo;doing nothing&amp;rsquo; be the ultimate strategy? Mew, Kurumi, and Mikael engage in a fierce debate over the pros and cons of active investing, which tries to beat the market, versus passive investing, which follows the market&amp;rsquo;s flow. Explore the allure of &amp;lsquo;auto-farming&amp;rsquo; your portfolio and the hidden risks behind it through data.</description></item><item><title>Is an 'Alt Season' Coming in the Second Half of 2025? The Hopeful vs. the Despairing View</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-18-altcoin-season-outlook/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-18-altcoin-season-outlook/</guid><description>Kurumi&amp;rsquo;s fiery optimism about Wall Street money flowing into RWA and AI themes clashes head-on with Mikael&amp;rsquo;s cold pessimism, which warns of macroeconomic uncertainty and regulatory risks. Will altcoin investors have reason to smile in the second half of 2025?</description></item><item><title>The SCHD and QQQ Combo: Is It Really That Powerful? (A Deep Dive into the Pros and Cons)</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-17-schd-and-qqq-combo/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-17-schd-and-qqq-combo/</guid><description>QQQ, the standard-bearer for growth stocks, and SCHD, the symbol of value. Is this the perfect combination? From the synergy of explosive growth and stable cash flow to the risks of US-only exposure and value traps, three unique characters break it all down.</description></item><item><title>Earning 'Rent' with a Small Investment? The Light and Shadow of REITs Investing</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-17-reits-light-and-shadow/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-17-reits-light-and-shadow/</guid><description>The dream of becoming a landlord and collecting rent with a small investment—is it possible with REITs? From the high dividend yields to the hidden interest rate risks and potential for principal loss, three unique characters delve into everything about REITs investing.</description></item><item><title>The Case for S&amp;P 500 ETFs for Beginners</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-15-why-sp500-etf/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-15-why-sp500-etf/</guid><description>Feeling lost about where to start with investing? Even Warren Buffett recommends S&amp;amp;P 500 ETFs. From the true meaning of &amp;lsquo;buy the market&amp;rsquo; to the risks of high valuations, three unique characters will explain the fundamentals of investing in a clear and simple way.</description></item><item><title>About Archive 03</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/about/</guid><description>(This is the English &amp;lsquo;About&amp;rsquo; page. The content will be filled in later.)</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/privacy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/privacy/</guid><description>Effective Date: June 27, 2025
Welcome to Archive 03 (the "Blog"). Your privacy is important to us. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, and protect your information when you visit our website.
1. Information We CollectOur Blog is designed to be accessible without requiring user registration. However, some information may be collected through third-party services to enhance your experience:
Comments via giscus:Information Collected: When you choose to leave a comment, you will be prompted to log in with your GitHub account.</description></item></channel></rss>