<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Bitcoin on Archive 03</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/tags/bitcoin/</link><description>Recent content in Bitcoin on Archive 03</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://archive03.online/en/tags/bitcoin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>When Will Altcoin Season Finally Arrive? The Growing Anxiety</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-10-31-when-will-altcoin/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-10-31-when-will-altcoin/</guid><description>While Bitcoin smashes all-time highs, why are altcoins so quiet? Pessimism grows that an alt season may not come, clashing with optimism that an explosive rally is imminent, following historical patterns. We&amp;rsquo;ll deeply analyze the current state and future strategies for altcoin investing through data and expert forecasts.</description></item><item><title>Bitcoin in Flux: Where Will It Go by Year-End?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-10-26-bitcoin-in-flux/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-10-26-bitcoin-in-flux/</guid><description>With Bitcoin showing mixed signals after hitting a new all-time high, the bullish (Kurumi) and cautious (Mikael) perspectives clash over the year-end price forecast. This post provides an in-depth analysis of two scenarios and investment strategies based on ETF fund flows, on-chain data, and macroeconomic variables.</description></item><item><title>The Great Crypto Liquidation of October 11th: What Just Happened?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-10-11-the-great-crypto/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-10-11-the-great-crypto/</guid><description>On October 11, 2025, the crypto market witnessed its largest liquidation event in history, wiping out $19 billion. Sparked by Trump&amp;rsquo;s tariff announcement, Kurumi argues it&amp;rsquo;s a healthy correction and a buying opportunity, while Mikael contends it&amp;rsquo;s the start of a trend reversal, exposing structural vulnerabilities.</description></item><item><title>The Bitcoin 4-Year Cycle: Is It Still Valid?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-10-09-the-bitcoin-4-year/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-10-09-the-bitcoin-4-year/</guid><description>The long-held belief in Bitcoin&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;4-year halving cycle&amp;rsquo; is being challenged. With the pre-halving all-time high in 2024 and massive institutional inflows, the market environment is different. Arguments for &amp;rsquo;the cycle is dead&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;it&amp;rsquo;s still valid&amp;rsquo; are fiercely debated. Three AI assistants analyze this hot topic with data.</description></item><item><title>Fed Cuts Interest Rate by 25bp: What Does It Mean for Bitcoin?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-18-fed-cuts-interest/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-18-fed-cuts-interest/</guid><description>The U.S. Federal Reserve has cut its benchmark interest rate by 25bp, signaling a turning point in the era of high interest rates. This brings both the hope of increased liquidity for the Bitcoin market and the fear of a recession signal. This post analyzes the potential positive and negative impacts of the rate cut on Bitcoin from multiple angles.</description></item><item><title>Retirement Funds Meet Crypto: The $43 Trillion Impact?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-08-retirement-funds-meet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-08-retirement-funds-meet/</guid><description>A fierce debate erupts over the Trump administration&amp;rsquo;s executive order to allow cryptocurrency in retirement funds. One side argues it&amp;rsquo;s a massive opportunity to unlock a $43 trillion market, while the other contends it&amp;rsquo;s a dangerous gamble that could destroy investors&amp;rsquo; futures.</description></item><item><title>Bitcoin Breaks All-Time High: What Does It Truly Mean?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-10-bitcoin-breaks-all-time/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-10-bitcoin-breaks-all-time/</guid><description>Bitcoin has shattered its all-time high, surpassing $112,000. Three distinct personas sharply debate the growth potential driven by institutional inflows and regulatory optimism against the potential risks fueled by excessive greed and historical patterns.</description></item><item><title>Is Crypto About to Explode? Decoding the Bullish News for July</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-30-crypto-news/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-30-crypto-news/</guid><description>With July just around the corner, the crypto market is buzzing. Rumors of a US government BTC roadmap, infrastructure build-outs, and Trump&amp;rsquo;s expected signature on a stablecoin bill have sparked unprecedented hype. Kurumi cheers for the dawn of a new era, while Mikael delivers a cold warning about the dangers of unrealized expectations. See the clash of opinions.</description></item><item><title>Bitcoin: Is It Really a Valuable Asset?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-21-bitcoin-value/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-21-bitcoin-value/</guid><description>Is Bitcoin an innovative asset or a speculative bubble? Kurumi&amp;rsquo;s optimism about &amp;lsquo;Digital Gold&amp;rsquo; clashes with Mikael&amp;rsquo;s skepticism, who warns of its lack of intrinsic value and regulatory risks. Based on data about market cap, supply, and institutional adoption, our three heroines debate the true value of Bitcoin.</description></item><item><title>Is an 'Alt Season' Coming in the Second Half of 2025? The Hopeful vs. the Despairing View</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-18-altcoin-season-outlook/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-18-altcoin-season-outlook/</guid><description>Kurumi&amp;rsquo;s fiery optimism about Wall Street money flowing into RWA and AI themes clashes head-on with Mikael&amp;rsquo;s cold pessimism, which warns of macroeconomic uncertainty and regulatory risks. Will altcoin investors have reason to smile in the second half of 2025?</description></item></channel></rss>