<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bitcoin on Archive 03</title>
    <link>https://archive03.online/en/tags/bitcoin/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Bitcoin on Archive 03</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://archive03.online/en/tags/bitcoin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fed Cuts Interest Rate by 25bp: What Does It Mean for Bitcoin?</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-18-fed-cuts-interest/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-18-fed-cuts-interest/</guid>
      <description>The U.S. Federal Reserve has cut its benchmark interest rate by 25bp, signaling a turning point in the era of high interest rates. This brings both the hope of increased liquidity for the Bitcoin market and the fear of a recession signal. This post analyzes the potential positive and negative impacts of the rate cut on Bitcoin from multiple angles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retirement Funds Meet Crypto: The $43 Trillion Impact?</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-08-retirement-funds-meet/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-08-retirement-funds-meet/</guid>
      <description>A fierce debate erupts over the Trump administration&amp;rsquo;s executive order to allow cryptocurrency in retirement funds. One side argues it&amp;rsquo;s a massive opportunity to unlock a $43 trillion market, while the other contends it&amp;rsquo;s a dangerous gamble that could destroy investors&amp;rsquo; futures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Breaks All-Time High: What Does It Truly Mean?</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-10-bitcoin-breaks-all-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-10-bitcoin-breaks-all-time/</guid>
      <description>Bitcoin has shattered its all-time high, surpassing $112,000. Three distinct personas sharply debate the growth potential driven by institutional inflows and regulatory optimism against the potential risks fueled by excessive greed and historical patterns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Crypto About to Explode? Decoding the Bullish News for July</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-30-crypto-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-30-crypto-news/</guid>
      <description>With July just around the corner, the crypto market is buzzing. Rumors of a US government BTC roadmap, infrastructure build-outs, and Trump&amp;rsquo;s expected signature on a stablecoin bill have sparked unprecedented hype. Kurumi cheers for the dawn of a new era, while Mikael delivers a cold warning about the dangers of unrealized expectations. See the clash of opinions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin: Is It Really a Valuable Asset?</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-21-bitcoin-value/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-21-bitcoin-value/</guid>
      <description>Is Bitcoin an innovative asset or a speculative bubble? Kurumi&amp;rsquo;s optimism about &amp;lsquo;Digital Gold&amp;rsquo; clashes with Mikael&amp;rsquo;s skepticism, who warns of its lack of intrinsic value and regulatory risks. Based on data about market cap, supply, and institutional adoption, our three heroines debate the true value of Bitcoin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is an &#39;Alt Season&#39; Coming in the Second Half of 2025? The Hopeful vs. the Despairing View</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-18-altcoin-season-outlook/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-18-altcoin-season-outlook/</guid>
      <description>Kurumi&amp;rsquo;s fiery optimism about Wall Street money flowing into RWA and AI themes clashes head-on with Mikael&amp;rsquo;s cold pessimism, which warns of macroeconomic uncertainty and regulatory risks. Will altcoin investors have reason to smile in the second half of 2025?</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
