<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Altcoin on Archive 03</title>
    <link>https://archive03.online/en/tags/altcoin/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Altcoin on Archive 03</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://archive03.online/en/tags/altcoin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How High Can Dogecoin ($DOGE) Go This Year?</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-14-how-high-can/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-14-how-high-can/</guid>
      <description>As expectations for an altcoin season grow with the decline in Bitcoin dominance, we explore the future of the original memecoin, Dogecoin ($DOGE). We analyze its growth potential from the massive catalyst of X (formerly Twitter) payment system integration against its inherent risk of lacking fundamentals, forecasting its price targets for the second half of the year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Altcoin King&#39; Ethereum: Price Outlook for H2 2025?</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-21-altcoin-king-ethereum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-21-altcoin-king-ethereum/</guid>
      <description>We analyze the price outlook for Ethereum in the second half of 2025, which is drawing intense interest with the launch of a U.S. spot ETF. Three characters engage in a sharp debate, weighing the massive tailwind of institutional capital inflow against potential risks like intensifying competition from Solana and macroeconomic uncertainty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is an &#39;Alt Season&#39; Coming in the Second Half of 2025? The Hopeful vs. the Despairing View</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-18-altcoin-season-outlook/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-18-altcoin-season-outlook/</guid>
      <description>Kurumi&amp;rsquo;s fiery optimism about Wall Street money flowing into RWA and AI themes clashes head-on with Mikael&amp;rsquo;s cold pessimism, which warns of macroeconomic uncertainty and regulatory risks. Will altcoin investors have reason to smile in the second half of 2025?</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
