<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cryptocurrency on Archive 03</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/tags/cryptocurrency/</link><description>Recent content in Cryptocurrency on Archive 03</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://archive03.online/en/tags/cryptocurrency/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why is Binance Coin ($BNB) Set to Benefit from the Alt-Season?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-15-why-is-binance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-15-why-is-binance/</guid><description>As excitement builds for an &amp;lsquo;alt-season&amp;rsquo; in the second half of 2025, we take a deep dive into the investment value of Binance Coin ($BNB), the native currency of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest exchange. While the BNB Chain&amp;rsquo;s technical advancements and strong token burn model boost its growth potential, it also faces clear limitations, such as its dependency on the Binance exchange and centralization risks. Three distinct characters debate whether BNB can become the biggest beneficiary of the alt-season and what potential dangers lie in wait.</description></item><item><title>How High Can Dogecoin ($DOGE) Go This Year?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-14-how-high-can/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-14-how-high-can/</guid><description>As expectations for an altcoin season grow with the decline in Bitcoin dominance, we explore the future of the original memecoin, Dogecoin ($DOGE). We analyze its growth potential from the massive catalyst of X (formerly Twitter) payment system integration against its inherent risk of lacking fundamentals, forecasting its price targets for the second half of the year.</description></item><item><title>Ethereum Breaks $4,000: Is This the Starting Gun for Altseason?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-09-ethereum-breaks-4000/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-09-ethereum-breaks-4000/</guid><description>With Ethereum surpassing the $4,000 mark, anticipation for a full-blown altseason is growing. Three distinct characters engage in a deep discussion centered on data, growth potential, and potential risks to determine whether this is the signal for a new opportunity or a warning sign of an overheated market.</description></item><item><title>Ondo Finance ($ONDO): A Deep Dive into the RWA Leader</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-08-ondo-finance-ondo/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-08-ondo-finance-ondo/</guid><description>A deep dive into Ondo Finance ($ONDO), the emerging leader in Real-World Asset (RWA) tokenization. Between its growth potential through a partnership with BlackRock and the potential risks of regulation and centralization, three characters fiercely debate the pros and cons of this new financial innovation.</description></item><item><title>Retirement Funds Meet Crypto: The $43 Trillion Impact?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-08-retirement-funds-meet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-08-retirement-funds-meet/</guid><description>A fierce debate erupts over the Trump administration&amp;rsquo;s executive order to allow cryptocurrency in retirement funds. One side argues it&amp;rsquo;s a massive opportunity to unlock a $43 trillion market, while the other contends it&amp;rsquo;s a dangerous gamble that could destroy investors&amp;rsquo; futures.</description></item><item><title>Is Now the Time to Buy Kaia ($Kaia) Coin? An Analysis and Investment Outlook</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-02-is-now-the/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-02-is-now-the/</guid><description>Three distinct personas debate the investment value of Kaia ($Kaia) coin, born from the merger of Kakao&amp;rsquo;s Klaytn and Line&amp;rsquo;s Finschia. They sharply analyze its overwhelming potential as Asia&amp;rsquo;s largest Web3 ecosystem against the potential risks of integrating two giant projects and their past limitations, arguing whether now is the right time to invest.</description></item><item><title>Solana, the 'Ethereum Killer': What's the Investment Outlook for 2025?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-02-solana-the-ethereum/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-02-solana-the-ethereum/</guid><description>A deep dive into the 2025 investment value of Solana ($SOL), the &amp;lsquo;Ethereum Killer&amp;rsquo; of the crypto market. Three distinct characters engage in a sharp debate over its growth potential, driven by overwhelming speed and explosive ecosystem growth, versus its fundamental risks concerning network stability and decentralization.</description></item><item><title>'Altcoin King' Ethereum: Price Outlook for H2 2025?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-21-altcoin-king-ethereum/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-21-altcoin-king-ethereum/</guid><description>We analyze the price outlook for Ethereum in the second half of 2025, which is drawing intense interest with the launch of a U.S. spot ETF. Three characters engage in a sharp debate, weighing the massive tailwind of institutional capital inflow against potential risks like intensifying competition from Solana and macroeconomic uncertainty.</description></item><item><title>The GENIUS Act: A Stroke of Genius That Could Change the Crypto Market?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-18-the-genius-act/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-18-the-genius-act/</guid><description>Three girls engage in a heated debate over the &amp;lsquo;GENIUS Act&amp;rsquo; passed by the U.S. Congress. Through Kurumi&amp;rsquo;s arguments for explosive growth from crypto&amp;rsquo;s institutional adoption and Mikael&amp;rsquo;s sharp analysis of the risks of contagion to the traditional financial system, they delve into the pros and cons of stablecoin regulation.</description></item><item><title>The 'DeFi Bank' $AAVE: What Kind of Coin Is It? Price Forecast and Analysis</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-15-the-defi-bank/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-15-the-defi-bank/</guid><description>A deep-dive analysis into the potential and risks of Aave ($AAVE), a leading DeFi lending protocol. Three characters engage in a sharp debate on its growth potential through its native stablecoin $GHO, and key issues like smart contract risks, liquidation, and regulatory challenges.</description></item><item><title>Bitcoin Breaks All-Time High: What Does It Truly Mean?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-10-bitcoin-breaks-all-time/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-10-bitcoin-breaks-all-time/</guid><description>Bitcoin has shattered its all-time high, surpassing $112,000. Three distinct personas sharply debate the growth potential driven by institutional inflows and regulatory optimism against the potential risks fueled by excessive greed and historical patterns.</description></item><item><title>XRP Down 40%: Time to Buy the Dip or Abandon Ship?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-27-xrp-review/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-27-xrp-review/</guid><description>Your friend bought Ripple (XRP) at the top and is now facing a huge loss. Is averaging down now an opportunity or a trap? Kurumi&amp;rsquo;s hope, fueled by the expected end of the SEC lawsuit, clashes with Mikael&amp;rsquo;s stark warning about extreme volatility and remaining risks. The three heroines provide an urgent diagnosis to save your friend&amp;rsquo;s portfolio.</description></item><item><title>Bitcoin: Is It Really a Valuable Asset?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-21-bitcoin-value/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-21-bitcoin-value/</guid><description>Is Bitcoin an innovative asset or a speculative bubble? Kurumi&amp;rsquo;s optimism about &amp;lsquo;Digital Gold&amp;rsquo; clashes with Mikael&amp;rsquo;s skepticism, who warns of its lack of intrinsic value and regulatory risks. Based on data about market cap, supply, and institutional adoption, our three heroines debate the true value of Bitcoin.</description></item><item><title>Is an 'Alt Season' Coming in the Second Half of 2025? The Hopeful vs. the Despairing View</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-18-altcoin-season-outlook/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-18-altcoin-season-outlook/</guid><description>Kurumi&amp;rsquo;s fiery optimism about Wall Street money flowing into RWA and AI themes clashes head-on with Mikael&amp;rsquo;s cold pessimism, which warns of macroeconomic uncertainty and regulatory risks. Will altcoin investors have reason to smile in the second half of 2025?</description></item></channel></rss>