<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Asset-Allocation on Archive 03</title>
    <link>https://archive03.online/en/tags/asset-allocation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Asset-Allocation on Archive 03</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://archive03.online/en/tags/asset-allocation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ray Dalio&#39;s Warning: How Should Individual Investors Respond?</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-05-ray-dalios-warning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-05-ray-dalios-warning/</guid>
      <description>In response to world-renowned investor Ray Dalio&amp;rsquo;s warning of a great collapse in order, growth-focused investment strategies (Kurumi) clash with risk-management-focused strategies (Mikael). This post explores new investment opportunities like cash-rich companies, consumer staples, and AI technology, while also discussing the importance of currency diversification, gold investment, and geopolitical risk management to find a balanced response for individual investors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Classic 60/40 Portfolio: Still Relevant in 2025?</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-04-the-classic-6040/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-04-the-classic-6040/</guid>
      <description>Three girls debate the validity of the classic &amp;lsquo;60/40 portfolio.&amp;rsquo; Kurumi champions its proven simplicity and stability, while Mikael warns of the potential for simultaneous stock and bond declines, arguing that times have changed. We analyze whether this traditional asset allocation strategy can still succeed today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VTI vs. VOO: Which Vanguard ETF Is Right for You?</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-03-vti-vs-voo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-03-vti-vs-voo/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s the timeless debate for US stock investors: VTI vs. VOO. Kurumi argues for VTI&amp;rsquo;s ability to capture future growth by buying the &amp;rsquo;total market,&amp;rsquo; while Mikael contends that VOO&amp;rsquo;s focus on 500 proven winners is more efficient. We break down the subtle philosophical differences and nearly identical performance data to help you choose.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 10-Year Rule: Why Long-Term Investing Is Your Greatest Ally</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-01-10-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-01-10-years/</guid>
      <description>Why is a 10-year investment horizon so critical? From harnessing the &amp;lsquo;magic of compounding&amp;rsquo; that Einstein praised, to using S&amp;amp;P 500 data to prove how time slashes market risk, and escaping the psychological traps of fear and greed. Three unique characters break down the three essential reasons for long-term investing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Start Investing in Bonds: Your Ally in a Bear Market?</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-21-bond-investment-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-21-bond-investment-guide/</guid>
      <description>Are bonds truly a safe haven when the stock market is volatile? From their negative correlation with stocks and predictable cash flow to the risks of interest rates and opportunity costs. Three unique characters break down everything you need to know about bond investing, including key ETFs like TLT, IEF, and AGG.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auto-Farming Your Investments? The Meaning, Advantages, and Limits of Passive Investing</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-18-passive-investing-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-18-passive-investing-guide/</guid>
      <description>In the world of investing, can &amp;lsquo;doing nothing&amp;rsquo; be the ultimate strategy? Mew, Kurumi, and Mikael engage in a fierce debate over the pros and cons of active investing, which tries to beat the market, versus passive investing, which follows the market&amp;rsquo;s flow. Explore the allure of &amp;lsquo;auto-farming&amp;rsquo; your portfolio and the hidden risks behind it through data.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
