<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Us-Stocks on Archive 03</title>
    <link>https://archive03.online/en/tags/us-stocks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Us-Stocks on Archive 03</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://archive03.online/en/tags/us-stocks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>An ETF That Pays Cash Weekly? An In-Depth Look at $MAGY&#39;s Pros and Cons</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-27-an-etf-that/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-27-an-etf-that/</guid>
      <description>$MAGY is an ETF that applies a covered call strategy to the &amp;lsquo;Magnificent Seven,&amp;rsquo; providing a high weekly distribution. While it offers the advantage of pursuing both growth and income, it also has clear drawbacks like extreme concentration and limited upside potential. This post provides a deep dive into how $MAGY works and its pros and cons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Energy Powerhouse $CEG: Is It Time to Invest? A Deep Dive into the Pros and Cons</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-24-energy-powerhouse-ceg/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-24-energy-powerhouse-ceg/</guid>
      <description>A deep dive into the investment appeal of Constellation Energy ($CEG), the largest nuclear power company in the U.S. We explore wise investment strategies by comparing the conflicting perspectives of growth expectations driven by the explosive increase in electricity demand in the AI era against the burden of an already high valuation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing the $SCHX ETF: Who Is It Best For?</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-21-analyzing-the-schx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-21-analyzing-the-schx/</guid>
      <description>We analyze the pros and cons of the $SCHX ETF, one of the cheapest ways to invest in the U.S. large-cap market. Its low 0.03% expense ratio and broad diversification are attractive, but the limitation of having to settle for market average returns is also clear. Discover if $SCHX is right for your portfolio through the debate between a stable investor pursuing the royal road of investing and an aggressive investor aiming for market-beating returns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a Pension with Dividends? Let&#39;s Dive into the $SCHD ETF</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-16-building-a-pension/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-16-building-a-pension/</guid>
      <description>A deep dive into America&amp;rsquo;s leading dividend growth ETF, $SCHD. Through a debate between Kurumi, who champions its steady cash flow and stability, and Mikael, who points out its growth limitations and interest rate risks, find out if $SCHD is the right fit for your retirement portfolio.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fallen Giant Intel: A Comeback Story? Analyzing Opportunities and Pitfalls</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-15-fallen-giant-intel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-15-fallen-giant-intel/</guid>
      <description>Intel, the once-dominant semiconductor empire, is attempting a revival with its &amp;lsquo;IDM 2.0&amp;rsquo; strategy. We conduct an in-depth analysis of Intel&amp;rsquo;s future, weighing the potential success of its foundry business and entry into the AI chip market against the technological uncertainty of its 18A process and a fiercely competitive landscape.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Warning from Howard Marks, the &#39;Sage of Wall Street&#39;: Is It Time to Sell?</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-17-a-warning-from/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-17-a-warning-from/</guid>
      <description>This post analyzes the current market&amp;rsquo;s overvaluation risk through Oaktree Capital&amp;rsquo;s Howard Marks&amp;rsquo; latest memo, &amp;lsquo;The Calculus of Value.&amp;rsquo; It explores the clash between Mikael&amp;rsquo;s warning of a &amp;lsquo;worrisome&amp;rsquo; situation where prices rise despite worsening fundamentals, and Kurumi&amp;rsquo;s optimism that the new era led by the AI revolution justifies high valuations, seeking a wise investment strategy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pharma ETF $PPH: A Deep Dive into Its Allure and Pitfalls</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-09-pharma-etf-pph/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-09-pharma-etf-pph/</guid>
      <description>A deep-dive analysis of the VanEck Pharmaceutical ETF ($PPH). Three characters debate the explosive growth potential of its concentrated strategy, focusing on innovators like Eli Lilly, against the clear pitfalls of high valuation and concentration risk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retirement Funds Meet Crypto: The $43 Trillion Impact?</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-08-retirement-funds-meet/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-08-retirement-funds-meet/</guid>
      <description>A fierce debate erupts over the Trump administration&amp;rsquo;s executive order to allow cryptocurrency in retirement funds. One side argues it&amp;rsquo;s a massive opportunity to unlock a $43 trillion market, while the other contends it&amp;rsquo;s a dangerous gamble that could destroy investors&amp;rsquo; futures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta Is Eating the Internet — Should You Invest Now?</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-07-whats-the-investment/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-07-whats-the-investment/</guid>
      <description>We analyze the investment prospects for Meta ($META), the empire of Facebook and Instagram. Amid the explosive growth of its AI-powered advertising business and the astronomical investment risks of Reality Labs, three characters engage in a fierce debate over Meta&amp;rsquo;s future value.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Cash is King!&#39; Why is Warren Buffett Continuously Selling Stocks?</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-03-cash-is-king/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-03-cash-is-king/</guid>
      <description>Berkshire Hathaway, led by the sage of investing Warren Buffett, is amassing a record level of cash and selling Apple stock. Dive into a sharp debate among three girls about whether this is a danger sign heralding a market crash or preparation for a massive opportunity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IonQ ($IONQ), a Leader in Quantum Computing: What&#39;s the Investment Outlook?</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-03-ionq-ionq-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-03-ionq-ionq-a/</guid>
      <description>IonQ ($IONQ) is a frontrunner in quantum computing technology, carrying high expectations of becoming the &amp;rsquo;next NVIDIA.&amp;rsquo; However, it also faces clear risks, such as a high valuation and financial instability. This post provides an in-depth analysis of IonQ&amp;rsquo;s growth potential and investment risks, offering a balanced perspective on this innovative company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Betting on Aerospace? An Analysis and Price Outlook for $ARKX</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-02-betting-on-aerospace/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-02-betting-on-aerospace/</guid>
      <description>An in-depth analysis of $ARKX, the space exploration ETF managed by Cathie Wood&amp;rsquo;s ARK Invest. Three girls discuss the growth potential of its portfolio, which invests in various sectors beyond pure space technology—such as defense, communications, and UAM—as well as the criticisms of it being a &amp;lsquo;quasi-space ETF&amp;rsquo; and its high volatility risks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coca-Cola ($KO): Is Warren Buffett&#39;s &#39;Golden Goose&#39; Still Viable in 2025?</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-18-coca-cola-ko-is/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-18-coca-cola-ko-is/</guid>
      <description>From a 2025 perspective, we re-evaluate the investment value of Coca-Cola ($KO), a stock beloved by investing legend Warren Buffett. Through a sharp debate between Kurumi, who champions its stability and brand power backed by 63 years of dividend increases, and Mikael, who points out the risks of stagnant growth and health trends, we analyze the pros and cons of this &amp;lsquo;Dividend King&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palantir ($PLTR), the Darling of the AI Age: Is It Still a Good Time to Invest?</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-13-palantir-pltr-the/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-13-palantir-pltr-the/</guid>
      <description>A fierce debate unfolds over the future of Palantir ($PLTR), the rising star of the AI era. We analyze the pros and cons of investing in $PLTR through the arguments of Kurumi, who champions its explosive commercial growth, and Mikael, who warns of its killer valuation and shareholder dilution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Could Robinhood Offer Commission-Free Trading?</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-09-how-could-robinhood/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-09-how-could-robinhood/</guid>
      <description>Unpacking the secret behind Robinhood&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;zero commission&amp;rsquo; model. Three characters debate the pros and cons of Payment for Order Flow (PFOF), weighing the innovation of &amp;lsquo;democratizing finance&amp;rsquo; against the risks of &amp;lsquo;hidden costs&amp;rsquo; and conflicts of interest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dividend Aristocrat Portfolio: Can I Build One Too?</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-08-the-dividend-aristocrat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-08-the-dividend-aristocrat/</guid>
      <description>Explore the allure and risks of a &amp;lsquo;Dividend Aristocrat&amp;rsquo; portfolio. Three distinct characters debate the pros (steady cash flow, compounding) and cons (limited growth, interest rate risk) of investing in stable companies that have increased dividends for over 25 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ray Dalio&#39;s Warning: How Should Individual Investors Respond?</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-05-ray-dalios-warning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-05-ray-dalios-warning/</guid>
      <description>In response to world-renowned investor Ray Dalio&amp;rsquo;s warning of a great collapse in order, growth-focused investment strategies (Kurumi) clash with risk-management-focused strategies (Mikael). This post explores new investment opportunities like cash-rich companies, consumer staples, and AI technology, while also discussing the importance of currency diversification, gold investment, and geopolitical risk management to find a balanced response for individual investors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JEPI vs. JEPQ: Stability or Growth? Unpacking the Ultimate Monthly Dividend ETFs</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-04-jepi-vs-jepq/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-04-jepi-vs-jepq/</guid>
      <description>A comparative analysis of America&amp;rsquo;s leading monthly dividend covered call ETFs, JEPI and JEPQ. We break down the pros and cons of the stable, S&amp;amp;P 500-based JEPI and the high-yield, Nasdaq 100-based JEPQ, helping you find the perfect fit for your investment style.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is the Fed&#39;s Rate Cut Really Good News for the Stock Market?</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-03-is-the-feds/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-03-is-the-feds/</guid>
      <description>Three characters clash over the impact of the U.S. Federal Reserve&amp;rsquo;s interest rate cut on the market. Kurumi predicts a bull market, cheering for a liquidity party, while Mikael strongly warns it&amp;rsquo;s a precursor to a recession. We analyze the two faces of rate cuts through historical data and explore the wise stance investors should take.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VTI vs. VOO: Which Vanguard ETF Is Right for You?</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-03-vti-vs-voo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-03-vti-vs-voo/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s the timeless debate for US stock investors: VTI vs. VOO. Kurumi argues for VTI&amp;rsquo;s ability to capture future growth by buying the &amp;rsquo;total market,&amp;rsquo; while Mikael contends that VOO&amp;rsquo;s focus on 500 proven winners is more efficient. We break down the subtle philosophical differences and nearly identical performance data to help you choose.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S&amp;P 500 Hits All-Time High: What Does It Mean?</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-29-sp500/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-29-sp500/</guid>
      <description>The S&amp;amp;P 500 has soared past 6,100 to a new record. Kurumi cheers for the dual engines of AI-driven earnings and easing geopolitical risks, while Mikael warns of Dot-com bubble valuations and &amp;lsquo;Extreme Greed.&amp;rsquo; Is it time to hit the accelerator, or should you be looking for the emergency exit?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia Hits All-Time Highs: Bubble or Just the Beginning?</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-26-nvidia-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-26-nvidia-review/</guid>
      <description>Nvidia has shattered its all-time high. Is this a celebration of the AI era, or a dangerous bubble? Kurumi&amp;rsquo;s optimism, fueled by the AI market&amp;rsquo;s structural growth and the powerful CUDA ecosystem, clashes head-on with Mikael&amp;rsquo;s warnings of extreme valuations and intensifying competition. Three unique characters engage in a fierce debate over Nvidia&amp;rsquo;s future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robinhood: Why Cathie Wood is Betting Big on $HOOD</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-25-robinhood/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-25-robinhood/</guid>
      <description>Cathie Wood keeps buying Robinhood ($HOOD). It&amp;rsquo;s a battleground between the innovation of &amp;lsquo;democratizing finance&amp;rsquo; and the critical risks of PFOF regulations and an SEC lawsuit. Kurumi sees a next-gen super-app, while Mikael warns of the regulatory sword. See the data and decide for yourself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google ($GOOGL) is &#39;Historically Cheap&#39;—Is It Time to Buy?</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-24-google-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-24-google-review/</guid>
      <description>Google ($GOOGL) has entered a historically undervalued range. Kurumi&amp;rsquo;s optimism about its explosive growth potential in AI and Cloud clashes head-on with Mikael&amp;rsquo;s pessimism, who warns of massive antitrust legal risks. Is investing in Google now a wise choice?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JEPI&#39;s 7% Yield: A Retirement Dream or a Total Return Trap?</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-22-jepi-etf-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-22-jepi-etf-analysis/</guid>
      <description>JEPI ETF offers a high distribution yield of over 7%, like monthly rent. Three unique characters fiercely debate the allure of its covered call strategy against its fatal flaws, including underperformance in bull markets and the risk of principal erosion. Is JEPI truly the best choice for those preparing for retirement?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Start Investing in Bonds: Your Ally in a Bear Market?</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-21-bond-investment-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-21-bond-investment-guide/</guid>
      <description>Are bonds truly a safe haven when the stock market is volatile? From their negative correlation with stocks and predictable cash flow to the risks of interest rates and opportunity costs. Three unique characters break down everything you need to know about bond investing, including key ETFs like TLT, IEF, and AGG.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The SCHD and QQQ Combo: Is It Really That Powerful? (A Deep Dive into the Pros and Cons)</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-17-schd-and-qqq-combo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-17-schd-and-qqq-combo/</guid>
      <description>QQQ, the standard-bearer for growth stocks, and SCHD, the symbol of value. Is this the perfect combination? From the synergy of explosive growth and stable cash flow to the risks of US-only exposure and value traps, three unique characters break it all down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earning &#39;Rent&#39; with a Small Investment? The Light and Shadow of REITs Investing</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-17-reits-light-and-shadow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-17-reits-light-and-shadow/</guid>
      <description>The dream of becoming a landlord and collecting rent with a small investment—is it possible with REITs? From the high dividend yields to the hidden interest rate risks and potential for principal loss, three unique characters delve into everything about REITs investing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Case for S&amp;P 500 ETFs for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-15-why-sp500-etf/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-15-why-sp500-etf/</guid>
      <description>Feeling lost about where to start with investing? Even Warren Buffett recommends S&amp;amp;P 500 ETFs. From the true meaning of &amp;lsquo;buy the market&amp;rsquo; to the risks of high valuations, three unique characters will explain the fundamentals of investing in a clear and simple way.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
