<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tech-Stocks on Archive 03</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/tags/tech-stocks/</link><description>Recent content in Tech-Stocks on Archive 03</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://archive03.online/en/tags/tech-stocks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Copying the 'God of Investing' Nancy Pelosi? Let's Dive into the $NANC ETF</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-10-27-copying-the-god/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-10-27-copying-the-god/</guid><description>A deep dive into the $NANC ETF, which tracks the stock trades of U.S. Democratic congress members. Is it a chance to replicate Nancy Pelosi&amp;rsquo;s phenomenal returns, or a trap with high fees and time lag issues? Three characters engage in a sharp debate over NANC&amp;rsquo;s investment appeal and potential risks.</description></item><item><title>IonQ ($IONQ), a Leader in Quantum Computing: What's the Investment Outlook?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-03-ionq-ionq-a/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-03-ionq-ionq-a/</guid><description>IonQ ($IONQ) is a frontrunner in quantum computing technology, carrying high expectations of becoming the &amp;rsquo;next NVIDIA.&amp;rsquo; However, it also faces clear risks, such as a high valuation and financial instability. This post provides an in-depth analysis of IonQ&amp;rsquo;s growth potential and investment risks, offering a balanced perspective on this innovative company.</description></item><item><title>Betting on Disruption: A Deep Dive into Cathie Wood's Investment Philosophy</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-12-betting-on-disruption/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-12-betting-on-disruption/</guid><description>This post explores the debate surrounding Cathie Wood&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;disruptive innovation&amp;rsquo; investment philosophy. It contrasts the growth strategy of betting boldly on future technologies for explosive returns with the risk management perspective that warns against the dangers of speculation that ignores valuation.</description></item></channel></rss>