<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Index-Fund on Archive 03</title>
    <link>https://archive03.online/en/tags/index-fund/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Index-Fund on Archive 03</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://archive03.online/en/tags/index-fund/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing the $SCHX ETF: Who Is It Best For?</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-21-analyzing-the-schx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-21-analyzing-the-schx/</guid>
      <description>We analyze the pros and cons of the $SCHX ETF, one of the cheapest ways to invest in the U.S. large-cap market. Its low 0.03% expense ratio and broad diversification are attractive, but the limitation of having to settle for market average returns is also clear. Discover if $SCHX is right for your portfolio through the debate between a stable investor pursuing the royal road of investing and an aggressive investor aiming for market-beating returns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JEPI vs. JEPQ: Stability or Growth? Unpacking the Ultimate Monthly Dividend ETFs</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-04-jepi-vs-jepq/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-04-jepi-vs-jepq/</guid>
      <description>A comparative analysis of America&amp;rsquo;s leading monthly dividend covered call ETFs, JEPI and JEPQ. We break down the pros and cons of the stable, S&amp;amp;P 500-based JEPI and the high-yield, Nasdaq 100-based JEPQ, helping you find the perfect fit for your investment style.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VTI vs. VOO: Which Vanguard ETF Is Right for You?</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-03-vti-vs-voo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-03-vti-vs-voo/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s the timeless debate for US stock investors: VTI vs. VOO. Kurumi argues for VTI&amp;rsquo;s ability to capture future growth by buying the &amp;rsquo;total market,&amp;rsquo; while Mikael contends that VOO&amp;rsquo;s focus on 500 proven winners is more efficient. We break down the subtle philosophical differences and nearly identical performance data to help you choose.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auto-Farming Your Investments? The Meaning, Advantages, and Limits of Passive Investing</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-18-passive-investing-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-18-passive-investing-guide/</guid>
      <description>In the world of investing, can &amp;lsquo;doing nothing&amp;rsquo; be the ultimate strategy? Mew, Kurumi, and Mikael engage in a fierce debate over the pros and cons of active investing, which tries to beat the market, versus passive investing, which follows the market&amp;rsquo;s flow. Explore the allure of &amp;lsquo;auto-farming&amp;rsquo; your portfolio and the hidden risks behind it through data.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
