<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fomc on Archive 03</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/tags/fomc/</link><description>Recent content in Fomc on Archive 03</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://archive03.online/en/tags/fomc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fed's December Rate Decision Looms... Is a Santa Claus Rally Coming?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-11-26-feds-december-rate/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-11-26-feds-december-rate/</guid><description>With the S&amp;amp;P 500 hovering around the 6,700 mark, all eyes are on the upcoming FOMC meeting scheduled for December 9-10. Recent dovish remarks from President John Williams have fueled expectations for a rate cut, but sticky 3% inflation and internal Fed divisions remain significant risks. Mew, Kurumi, and Mikael provide an in-depth analysis of the potential for a &amp;lsquo;Santa Claus Rally&amp;rsquo; and the looming &amp;rsquo;tariff risk&amp;rsquo;.</description></item><item><title>Fed Cuts Interest Rate by 25bp: What Does It Mean for Bitcoin?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-18-fed-cuts-interest/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-18-fed-cuts-interest/</guid><description>The U.S. Federal Reserve has cut its benchmark interest rate by 25bp, signaling a turning point in the era of high interest rates. This brings both the hope of increased liquidity for the Bitcoin market and the fear of a recession signal. This post analyzes the potential positive and negative impacts of the rate cut on Bitcoin from multiple angles.</description></item><item><title>Market Expects September Rate Cut: Will the 'Money Move' Begin?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-30-market-expects-september/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-30-market-expects-september/</guid><description>The U.S. Federal Reserve&amp;rsquo;s September rate cut expectations are at an all-time high. Is this a signal for the start of a new bull market, or a precursor to a recession? We analyze the direction of the &amp;lsquo;money move&amp;rsquo; through a sharp debate between Kurumi, who anticipates a liquidity rally, and Mikael, who warns of hidden risks.</description></item><item><title>Why Did Trump Call Powell 'Stupid'?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-20-trump-criticizes-powell/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-20-trump-criticizes-powell/</guid><description>President Trump has publicly criticized Fed Chair Powell, pressuring him to cut interest rates. Mew, Kurumi, and Mikael sharply analyze the current situation, where the hope for a short-term market boost clashes with the immense risk of undermining the central bank&amp;rsquo;s independence.</description></item></channel></rss>