<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Rwa on Archive 03</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/tags/rwa/</link><description>Recent content in Rwa on Archive 03</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://archive03.online/en/tags/rwa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Chainlink ($LINK): A Deep Dive into the Oracle King, Price Analysis, and Future Outlook</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-30-chainlink-link-a/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-30-chainlink-link-a/</guid><description>As the core infrastructure connecting blockchains to the real world, does Chainlink ($LINK) have a bright future? We dive into a sharp debate between Kurumi, who champions Chainlink&amp;rsquo;s monopolistic position and growth potential as a Web3 necessity, and Mikael, who warns of potential risks like market dependency and uncertain tokenomics, to analyze the pros and cons of investing in $LINK.</description></item><item><title>Ondo Finance ($ONDO): A Deep Dive into the RWA Leader</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-08-ondo-finance-ondo/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-08-ondo-finance-ondo/</guid><description>A deep dive into Ondo Finance ($ONDO), the emerging leader in Real-World Asset (RWA) tokenization. Between its growth potential through a partnership with BlackRock and the potential risks of regulation and centralization, three characters fiercely debate the pros and cons of this new financial innovation.</description></item><item><title>Is an 'Alt Season' Coming in the Second Half of 2025? The Hopeful vs. the Despairing View</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-18-altcoin-season-outlook/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-18-altcoin-season-outlook/</guid><description>Kurumi&amp;rsquo;s fiery optimism about Wall Street money flowing into RWA and AI themes clashes head-on with Mikael&amp;rsquo;s cold pessimism, which warns of macroeconomic uncertainty and regulatory risks. Will altcoin investors have reason to smile in the second half of 2025?</description></item></channel></rss>