<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Value-Investing on Archive 03</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/tags/value-investing/</link><description>Recent content in Value-Investing on Archive 03</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://archive03.online/en/tags/value-investing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Warning from Howard Marks, the 'Sage of Wall Street': Is It Time to Sell?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-17-a-warning-from/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-17-a-warning-from/</guid><description>This post analyzes the current market&amp;rsquo;s overvaluation risk through Oaktree Capital&amp;rsquo;s Howard Marks&amp;rsquo; latest memo, &amp;lsquo;The Calculus of Value.&amp;rsquo; It explores the clash between Mikael&amp;rsquo;s warning of a &amp;lsquo;worrisome&amp;rsquo; situation where prices rise despite worsening fundamentals, and Kurumi&amp;rsquo;s optimism that the new era led by the AI revolution justifies high valuations, seeking a wise investment strategy.</description></item><item><title>'Cash is King!' Why is Warren Buffett Continuously Selling Stocks?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-03-cash-is-king/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-03-cash-is-king/</guid><description>Berkshire Hathaway, led by the sage of investing Warren Buffett, is amassing a record level of cash and selling Apple stock. Dive into a sharp debate among three girls about whether this is a danger sign heralding a market crash or preparation for a massive opportunity.</description></item><item><title>Decoding a Wall Street Giant: The Richard Bernstein Method</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-02-richard-bernstein/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-02-richard-bernstein/</guid><description>Three unique characters dissect the investment philosophy of Wall Street giant Richard Bernstein. A fierce debate ensues over his top-down &amp;lsquo;see the forest&amp;rsquo; approach and the contrarian core of enduring pain. Learn his wisdom of finding market opportunities through corporate profit cycles.</description></item><item><title>The 10-Year Rule: Why Long-Term Investing Is Your Greatest Ally</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-01-10-years/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-01-10-years/</guid><description>Why is a 10-year investment horizon so critical? From harnessing the &amp;lsquo;magic of compounding&amp;rsquo; that Einstein praised, to using S&amp;amp;P 500 data to prove how time slashes market risk, and escaping the psychological traps of fear and greed. Three unique characters break down the three essential reasons for long-term investing.</description></item><item><title>Glenn Gould's Forte: The Pianist's Secret to Winning at the Market</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-30-glenn-gould/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-30-glenn-gould/</guid><description>Discover the surprising investing prowess of legendary pianist Glenn Gould. How did he tune out market noise to become a successful long-term investor? Three unique characters analyze his investment philosophy and portfolio, exploring the two sides of his genius: disciplined, emotion-free principles and a profound belief in what he loved.</description></item><item><title>Why the Stock Market Isn't a Zero-Sum Game</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-25-non-zero-sum-game/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-25-non-zero-sum-game/</guid><description>Did you think stock investing was a game of taking someone else&amp;rsquo;s money? From the theory that it&amp;rsquo;s a &amp;lsquo;positive-sum game&amp;rsquo; where the whole pie grows thanks to corporate value creation, to the reality that short-term trading has the brutal nature of a &amp;lsquo;zero-sum game&amp;rsquo;—our three experts clearly define the true nature of investing.</description></item></channel></rss>