<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rate-Cut on Archive 03</title>
    <link>https://archive03.online/en/tags/rate-cut/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Rate-Cut on Archive 03</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://archive03.online/en/tags/rate-cut/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Market Expects September Rate Cut: Will the &#39;Money Move&#39; Begin?</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-30-market-expects-september/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-30-market-expects-september/</guid>
      <description>The U.S. Federal Reserve&amp;rsquo;s September rate cut expectations are at an all-time high. Is this a signal for the start of a new bull market, or a precursor to a recession? We analyze the direction of the &amp;lsquo;money move&amp;rsquo; through a sharp debate between Kurumi, who anticipates a liquidity rally, and Mikael, who warns of hidden risks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powell&#39;s Dovish Turn: The Fallout from the 2025 Jackson Hole Meeting</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-23-powells-dovish-turn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-23-powells-dovish-turn/</guid>
      <description>At the 2025 Jackson Hole meeting, Fed Chair Jerome Powell pivoted to a dovish stance, sparking market euphoria. As expectations for a rate cut grow, three distinct characters engage in a fierce debate, weighing the optimism against the underlying risks of an economic slowdown and inflation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is the Fed&#39;s Rate Cut Really Good News for the Stock Market?</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-03-is-the-feds/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-03-is-the-feds/</guid>
      <description>Three characters clash over the impact of the U.S. Federal Reserve&amp;rsquo;s interest rate cut on the market. Kurumi predicts a bull market, cheering for a liquidity party, while Mikael strongly warns it&amp;rsquo;s a precursor to a recession. We analyze the two faces of rate cuts through historical data and explore the wise stance investors should take.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
