<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolio on Archive 03</title>
    <link>https://archive03.online/en/tags/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Portfolio on Archive 03</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://archive03.online/en/tags/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Dividend Aristocrat Portfolio: Can I Build One Too?</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-08-the-dividend-aristocrat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-08-the-dividend-aristocrat/</guid>
      <description>Explore the allure and risks of a &amp;lsquo;Dividend Aristocrat&amp;rsquo; portfolio. Three distinct characters debate the pros (steady cash flow, compounding) and cons (limited growth, interest rate risk) of investing in stable companies that have increased dividends for over 25 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ray Dalio&#39;s Warning: How Should Individual Investors Respond?</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-05-ray-dalios-warning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-05-ray-dalios-warning/</guid>
      <description>In response to world-renowned investor Ray Dalio&amp;rsquo;s warning of a great collapse in order, growth-focused investment strategies (Kurumi) clash with risk-management-focused strategies (Mikael). This post explores new investment opportunities like cash-rich companies, consumer staples, and AI technology, while also discussing the importance of currency diversification, gold investment, and geopolitical risk management to find a balanced response for individual investors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Classic 60/40 Portfolio: Still Relevant in 2025?</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-04-the-classic-6040/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-04-the-classic-6040/</guid>
      <description>Three girls debate the validity of the classic &amp;lsquo;60/40 portfolio.&amp;rsquo; Kurumi champions its proven simplicity and stability, while Mikael warns of the potential for simultaneous stock and bond declines, arguing that times have changed. We analyze whether this traditional asset allocation strategy can still succeed today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The SCHD and QQQ Combo: Is It Really That Powerful? (A Deep Dive into the Pros and Cons)</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-17-schd-and-qqq-combo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-17-schd-and-qqq-combo/</guid>
      <description>QQQ, the standard-bearer for growth stocks, and SCHD, the symbol of value. Is this the perfect combination? From the synergy of explosive growth and stable cash flow to the risks of US-only exposure and value traps, three unique characters break it all down.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
