<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Digital-Asset on Archive 03</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/tags/digital-asset/</link><description>Recent content in Digital-Asset on Archive 03</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://archive03.online/en/tags/digital-asset/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ripple (XRP): Time to Buy or Time to Sell?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-10-10-ripple-xrp-time/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-10-10-ripple-xrp-time/</guid><description>After Ripple (XRP)&amp;rsquo;s virtual victory in its long legal battle with the SEC, investors are wondering whether now is a buying opportunity or a time to take profits. Optimists highlight the resolution of legal risks and high growth potential, while skeptics warn that the good news is already priced in and structural risks remain. This post provides an in-depth analysis of the key arguments and risks of investing in XRP to suggest a wise investment strategy.</description></item><item><title>Why is Binance Coin ($BNB) Set to Benefit from the Alt-Season?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-15-why-is-binance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-15-why-is-binance/</guid><description>As excitement builds for an &amp;lsquo;alt-season&amp;rsquo; in the second half of 2025, we take a deep dive into the investment value of Binance Coin ($BNB), the native currency of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest exchange. While the BNB Chain&amp;rsquo;s technical advancements and strong token burn model boost its growth potential, it also faces clear limitations, such as its dependency on the Binance exchange and centralization risks. Three distinct characters debate whether BNB can become the biggest beneficiary of the alt-season and what potential dangers lie in wait.</description></item></channel></rss>