<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Digital-Assets on Archive 03</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/tags/digital-assets/</link><description>Recent content in Digital-Assets on Archive 03</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://archive03.online/en/tags/digital-assets/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bitcoin in Flux: Where Will It Go by Year-End?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-10-26-bitcoin-in-flux/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-10-26-bitcoin-in-flux/</guid><description>With Bitcoin showing mixed signals after hitting a new all-time high, the bullish (Kurumi) and cautious (Mikael) perspectives clash over the year-end price forecast. This post provides an in-depth analysis of two scenarios and investment strategies based on ETF fund flows, on-chain data, and macroeconomic variables.</description></item><item><title>Ondo Finance ($ONDO): A Deep Dive into the RWA Leader</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-08-ondo-finance-ondo/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-08-ondo-finance-ondo/</guid><description>A deep dive into Ondo Finance ($ONDO), the emerging leader in Real-World Asset (RWA) tokenization. Between its growth potential through a partnership with BlackRock and the potential risks of regulation and centralization, three characters fiercely debate the pros and cons of this new financial innovation.</description></item><item><title>Solana, the 'Ethereum Killer': What's the Investment Outlook for 2025?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-02-solana-the-ethereum/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-02-solana-the-ethereum/</guid><description>A deep dive into the 2025 investment value of Solana ($SOL), the &amp;lsquo;Ethereum Killer&amp;rsquo; of the crypto market. Three distinct characters engage in a sharp debate over its growth potential, driven by overwhelming speed and explosive ecosystem growth, versus its fundamental risks concerning network stability and decentralization.</description></item><item><title>The GENIUS Act: A Stroke of Genius That Could Change the Crypto Market?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-18-the-genius-act/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-18-the-genius-act/</guid><description>Three girls engage in a heated debate over the &amp;lsquo;GENIUS Act&amp;rsquo; passed by the U.S. Congress. Through Kurumi&amp;rsquo;s arguments for explosive growth from crypto&amp;rsquo;s institutional adoption and Mikael&amp;rsquo;s sharp analysis of the risks of contagion to the traditional financial system, they delve into the pros and cons of stablecoin regulation.</description></item><item><title>Bitcoin Breaks All-Time High: What Does It Truly Mean?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-10-bitcoin-breaks-all-time/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-10-bitcoin-breaks-all-time/</guid><description>Bitcoin has shattered its all-time high, surpassing $112,000. Three distinct personas sharply debate the growth potential driven by institutional inflows and regulatory optimism against the potential risks fueled by excessive greed and historical patterns.</description></item></channel></rss>