<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Passive-Investing on Archive 03</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/tags/passive-investing/</link><description>Recent content in Passive-Investing on Archive 03</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://archive03.online/en/tags/passive-investing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Analyzing the $SCHX ETF: Who Is It Best For?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-21-analyzing-the-schx/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-21-analyzing-the-schx/</guid><description>We analyze the pros and cons of the $SCHX ETF, one of the cheapest ways to invest in the U.S. large-cap market. Its low 0.03% expense ratio and broad diversification are attractive, but the limitation of having to settle for market average returns is also clear. Discover if $SCHX is right for your portfolio through the debate between a stable investor pursuing the royal road of investing and an aggressive investor aiming for market-beating returns.</description></item><item><title>How Did John Bogle's 'Buy Everything' Philosophy Change the History of Investing?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-03-john-bogle/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-03-john-bogle/</guid><description>We delve into the investment philosophy of John Bogle, the &amp;lsquo;Saint of Wall Street.&amp;rsquo; Kurumi explains how the revolutionary idea of &amp;rsquo;low-cost index funds&amp;rsquo; provided individual investors with a new path to wealth accumulation, while Mikael points out the limitations and structural risks of a strategy that can only ever achieve the &amp;lsquo;average.&amp;rsquo; How should we apply the wisdom of this so-called cornerstone of investing?</description></item><item><title>Auto-Farming Your Investments? The Meaning, Advantages, and Limits of Passive Investing</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-18-passive-investing-guide/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-18-passive-investing-guide/</guid><description>In the world of investing, can &amp;lsquo;doing nothing&amp;rsquo; be the ultimate strategy? Mew, Kurumi, and Mikael engage in a fierce debate over the pros and cons of active investing, which tries to beat the market, versus passive investing, which follows the market&amp;rsquo;s flow. Explore the allure of &amp;lsquo;auto-farming&amp;rsquo; your portfolio and the hidden risks behind it through data.</description></item></channel></rss>