<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Recession on Archive 03</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/tags/recession/</link><description>Recent content in Recession on Archive 03</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://archive03.online/en/tags/recession/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fed Cuts Interest Rate by 25bp: What Does It Mean for Bitcoin?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-18-fed-cuts-interest/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-09-18-fed-cuts-interest/</guid><description>The U.S. Federal Reserve has cut its benchmark interest rate by 25bp, signaling a turning point in the era of high interest rates. This brings both the hope of increased liquidity for the Bitcoin market and the fear of a recession signal. This post analyzes the potential positive and negative impacts of the rate cut on Bitcoin from multiple angles.</description></item><item><title>Market Expects September Rate Cut: Will the 'Money Move' Begin?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-30-market-expects-september/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-30-market-expects-september/</guid><description>The U.S. Federal Reserve&amp;rsquo;s September rate cut expectations are at an all-time high. Is this a signal for the start of a new bull market, or a precursor to a recession? We analyze the direction of the &amp;lsquo;money move&amp;rsquo; through a sharp debate between Kurumi, who anticipates a liquidity rally, and Mikael, who warns of hidden risks.</description></item><item><title>Is the Fed's Rate Cut Really Good News for the Stock Market?</title><link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-03-is-the-feds/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-03-is-the-feds/</guid><description>Three characters clash over the impact of the U.S. Federal Reserve&amp;rsquo;s interest rate cut on the market. Kurumi predicts a bull market, cheering for a liquidity party, while Mikael strongly warns it&amp;rsquo;s a precursor to a recession. We analyze the two faces of rate cuts through historical data and explore the wise stance investors should take.</description></item></channel></rss>