<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stablecoin on Archive 03</title>
    <link>https://archive03.online/en/tags/stablecoin/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Stablecoin on Archive 03</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://archive03.online/en/tags/stablecoin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The GENIUS Act: A Stroke of Genius That Could Change the Crypto Market?</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-18-the-genius-act/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-18-the-genius-act/</guid>
      <description>Three girls engage in a heated debate over the &amp;lsquo;GENIUS Act&amp;rsquo; passed by the U.S. Congress. Through Kurumi&amp;rsquo;s arguments for explosive growth from crypto&amp;rsquo;s institutional adoption and Mikael&amp;rsquo;s sharp analysis of the risks of contagion to the traditional financial system, they delve into the pros and cons of stablecoin regulation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Crypto About to Explode? Decoding the Bullish News for July</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-30-crypto-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-30-crypto-news/</guid>
      <description>With July just around the corner, the crypto market is buzzing. Rumors of a US government BTC roadmap, infrastructure build-outs, and Trump&amp;rsquo;s expected signature on a stablecoin bill have sparked unprecedented hype. Kurumi cheers for the dawn of a new era, while Mikael delivers a cold warning about the dangers of unrealized expectations. See the clash of opinions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dawn of the Digital Won: What a KRW Stablecoin Means for Investors</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-25-won-stable-coin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-06-25-won-stable-coin/</guid>
      <description>The launch of a Korean Won stablecoin: Will it be the next STO craze or a new investment frontier? Kurumi bets on the explosive growth of issuer stocks and mainnet tokens, while Mikael warns of priced-in hype and the limits of a domestic-only market. We analyze the opportunities and pitfalls of owning a piece of future financial infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
