<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Growth-Stocks on Archive 03</title>
    <link>https://archive03.online/en/tags/growth-stocks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Growth-Stocks on Archive 03</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://archive03.online/en/tags/growth-stocks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Market Expects September Rate Cut: Will the &#39;Money Move&#39; Begin?</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-30-market-expects-september/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-30-market-expects-september/</guid>
      <description>The U.S. Federal Reserve&amp;rsquo;s September rate cut expectations are at an all-time high. Is this a signal for the start of a new bull market, or a precursor to a recession? We analyze the direction of the &amp;lsquo;money move&amp;rsquo; through a sharp debate between Kurumi, who anticipates a liquidity rally, and Mikael, who warns of hidden risks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pharma ETF $PPH: A Deep Dive into Its Allure and Pitfalls</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-09-pharma-etf-pph/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-09-pharma-etf-pph/</guid>
      <description>A deep-dive analysis of the VanEck Pharmaceutical ETF ($PPH). Three characters debate the explosive growth potential of its concentrated strategy, focusing on innovators like Eli Lilly, against the clear pitfalls of high valuation and concentration risk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta Is Eating the Internet — Should You Invest Now?</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-07-whats-the-investment/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-07-whats-the-investment/</guid>
      <description>We analyze the investment prospects for Meta ($META), the empire of Facebook and Instagram. Amid the explosive growth of its AI-powered advertising business and the astronomical investment risks of Reality Labs, three characters engage in a fierce debate over Meta&amp;rsquo;s future value.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IonQ ($IONQ), a Leader in Quantum Computing: What&#39;s the Investment Outlook?</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-03-ionq-ionq-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-03-ionq-ionq-a/</guid>
      <description>IonQ ($IONQ) is a frontrunner in quantum computing technology, carrying high expectations of becoming the &amp;rsquo;next NVIDIA.&amp;rsquo; However, it also faces clear risks, such as a high valuation and financial instability. This post provides an in-depth analysis of IonQ&amp;rsquo;s growth potential and investment risks, offering a balanced perspective on this innovative company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Betting on Aerospace? An Analysis and Price Outlook for $ARKX</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-02-betting-on-aerospace/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-08-02-betting-on-aerospace/</guid>
      <description>An in-depth analysis of $ARKX, the space exploration ETF managed by Cathie Wood&amp;rsquo;s ARK Invest. Three girls discuss the growth potential of its portfolio, which invests in various sectors beyond pure space technology—such as defense, communications, and UAM—as well as the criticisms of it being a &amp;lsquo;quasi-space ETF&amp;rsquo; and its high volatility risks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palantir ($PLTR), the Darling of the AI Age: Is It Still a Good Time to Invest?</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-13-palantir-pltr-the/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-13-palantir-pltr-the/</guid>
      <description>A fierce debate unfolds over the future of Palantir ($PLTR), the rising star of the AI era. We analyze the pros and cons of investing in $PLTR through the arguments of Kurumi, who champions its explosive commercial growth, and Mikael, who warns of its killer valuation and shareholder dilution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Betting on Disruption: A Deep Dive into Cathie Wood&#39;s Investment Philosophy</title>
      <link>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-12-betting-on-disruption/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://archive03.online/en/reports/2025-07-12-betting-on-disruption/</guid>
      <description>This post explores the debate surrounding Cathie Wood&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;disruptive innovation&amp;rsquo; investment philosophy. It contrasts the growth strategy of betting boldly on future technologies for explosive returns with the risk management perspective that warns against the dangers of speculation that ignores valuation.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
